<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<dc>
<title>Research and Training Opportunities at NIH</title>
<identifier>http://eot.us.archive.org/eot08/20080916072205/training.nih.gov/</identifier>
<provenance>http://www.training.nih.gov/</provenance>
<date>2008-09-16</date>
<date>2009-05-10</date>
<description>Featuring biomedical research and training opportunities at the National Institutes of Health. Site offers rich variety of opportunities for students, postdocs, physicians and senior investigators. Multimedia catolog describing dozens of training programs. Interactive listings allow immediate on-line application for hundreds of openings. Hypertext calendar provides constantly updated information on upcoming lectures, seminars, workshops and conferences. Links to related sites and resources.</description>
<subject>research training NIH postdoctoral laboratory clinical science biology biomedical student medicine medical jobs employment opportunities physician genetic cancer HIV AIDS national institutes health career internship fellowship research training NIH postdoctoral laboratory clinical science biology biomedical student medicine medical jobs employment opportunities physician genetic cancer HIV AIDS national institutes health career internship fellowship research training NIH postdoctoral laboratory clinical science biology biomedical student medicine medical jobs employment opportunities physician genetic cancer HIV AIDS national institutes health career internship fellowship research training NIH postdoctoral laboratory clinical science biology biomedical student medicine medical jobs employment opportunities physician genetic cancer HIV AIDS national institutes health career internship fellowship research training NIH postdoctoral laboratory clinical science biology biomedical student medicine medical jobs employment opportunities physician genetic cancer HIV AIDS national institutes health career internship fellowship</subject>
<type>web site</type>
<format>text</format>
<coverage>Executive</coverage>
<source>training</source>
<source>nih</source>
<relation>http://crawls.archive.org/collections/eot08/</relation>
</dc>
